http://www.caverion.com/about-us/privacy-notice

Scalable digital solutions and smart technologies
Building Management System (BMS)
Automation
Building Management System (BMS)
Flaggings
Determination of acquisition costs of Caverion shares in taxation
Effective date: 16 May 2018
As a data controller, Caverion Corporation is required to protect your personal information, and our aim is to make you feel secure when we process your personal data. We protect your privacy in compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation as well as all other applicable laws.
We encourage you to read this privacy notice thoroughly.
1. Who is collecting your personal data
When we refer to Caverion in this privacy notice, we mean Caverion Corporation and its affiliates listed in Caverion Corporation’s latest financial statement available. Caverion is a group of companies whose parent company is listed on the Nasdaq Helsinki. Caverion Corporation has its domicile in Helsinki, Finland.
Contact information
Caverion Group
Kimmo Nikulainen
Torpantie 2, 01650 Vantaa
Phone: +358 10 4071
Email: communications@caverion.com
Organisation number: 2534127-4
2. Protecting personal data
We take privacy and security of your personal data seriously. All personal data you provide to Caverion is being stored on secure servers and only employees and third parties who need to access to this information shall have access to your personal data. Those individuals who have access to the personal data are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information. Caverion and our service providers will always take all reasonable measures to make sure your personal data is being protected.
3. Definitions
“Caverion” or “us” or “we” or “company” refer to Caverion Corporation and its affiliates that may process your personal data as mentioned in clause 1 above.
“personal data” or “personal information” refer to all kinds of information that directly or indirectly identify an individual or can be used in combination with other information to identify an individual. Examples of personal information: Name, phone number, email address, date of birth.
“sensitive personal data” or “sensitive personal information” refer to certain special categories of personal data and is information of more sensitive nature of the individual. Examples of personal information: racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership.
“user(s)” or “you” or “data subject” or “person” refer to  user(s) of our websites, users of our services or other persons external to Caverion that are providing personal data to Caverion.
“website” refer to website reachable via the following primary URL caverion.com, as well as our country domains, campaign landing pages (e.g. hub.caverion.com) and online recruiting services (e.g. careers.fi/caverion).
4. Information we collect & Purposes of collecting personal data
We will only collect such personal information that is relevant for the purposes described in this privacy notice.  We collect information that is (a) provided by you but also (b) information collected automatically or (c) obtained through other external sources. We describe here how we handle personal data of different data subject groups. Note that we sometimes combine information we receive from you, information collected online, information collected offline and information collected from third party sources, always in compliance with applicable laws and regulations pertaining to processing of personal data.
We will use your personal data only for the purposes stated in this privacy notice, unless we receive your consent for other purposes.
Expand all
Collapse all
Privacy notice
4.1. Website users
Information collected of you
You do not need to give your personal data to be able to use Caverion websites. We collect only such personal data as is provided voluntarily by the users of our website.
Consent (a)
Contact details work (e.g. address, email, phone) (a)
Demographic data (e.g. age, gender, nationality, language) (a) (b)
Diet (for events) (a)
Email tracking (e.g. open rates, clicks, date and time of your activities) (b)
Employer details (e.g. company name, address, previous employer) (a)
Interests (a) (b)
IP address (b)
Name (e.g. first name, last name) (a)
Position data (e.g. title, organizational unit, job) (a)
Social media public profile data (c)
Survey response data (a)User accounts (e.g. user name, password for system) (b) (c)
Web site visits (e.g. website, cookies, browser details, date and time of your visit, user behaviour) (b)
Purposes of collecting data
Advertising: We can use your personal information to display advertising on our website or on third party sites. Some of our third-party partners use cookies or similar technologies to provide you advertising based on your browsing activities and interests. Read more from our Cookie notice
Build potential customer relationship: We collect personal data of potential customers or contact persons of customers to our customer database. We collect this personal data to be in contact with you, identify your needs and to offer you best solutions.
Communications & videoconferencing: We store contact information for communication purposes for contacting and co-operation.
Competitions: We may organise competitions where you submit your contact details when participating. We will use this information to be able to contact competition winner(s).
Complaints & claims: We need your personal data to help us manage your complaint, if you are not satisfied with us.
Event management: We organise and host or participate to events and/or exhibitions. We use your information to e.g. invite you to events, share information about the events, ask for your feedback after the event and other event related purposes (e.g. special diets).
Feedback collection: We sometimes ask your feedback of various items. We use this information e.g. to improve our operations and services.
Identity administration: We use this personal information to reliably identify you, in case of e.g. data subject requests, system access.
Improvement of our performance: We use personal data to improve our services, offering, customer experience and communication.
Internal training purposes: We might use your information for internal training purposes as an example to ensure our employees have the knowledge and expertise they need to provide you the best possible performance.
Legal obligation: We will use your personal data to comply with the laws and regulations (e.g. court order).
Marketing: We might use your personal data for marketing purposes if you have indicated your consent and if we think our products, services, offers or third party solutions may interest you. We may also target specific marketing messages based on your user behaviour on our website. We might contact you about them through email, SMS or phone. You can Opt-out marketing communications at any time by filling out this form.  Read also our Cookie notice.
Personalisation: We might use your personal information to personalise the content of the website, emails or other type of digital assets based on your user behaviour. We use this information to offer you better performance and match your interests to our offering.
Records & administration: We need to have comprehensive records of how we process your personal information.
Reporting and analytics: We sometimes use your information to reporting and analytics to enable us to improve our products, services and customer experience.
Surveys: We may invite you to take part of our surveys. If you decide to take part we will use this information to improve our operations and performance.
Track user behaviour: We might use your information to track your activity on our websites or apps. That will help us to understand your interests and offer you better service. We can also target you specific marketing messages based on your behaviour. This requires your consent and you can opt-out anytime from receiving marketing messages from us. Read also our Cookie notice.
Website development: We use your information to improve our websites functionality, performance, user experience and security.
4.2. Customers
Information collected of you
We need information for various purposes if you are our customer. Most of the information is provided by you, but we collect some information also from other sources. Based on your behaviour on our website, we might interpret your visits to certain pages as your interest areas and store that information to our customer databases. We will do this only if you have given us your contact details in a contact form or subscribed our newsletter. Also if you are a new employee of our existing customer, your personal details can be provided to us by your line manager or colleague and we will update the data accordingly to our customer database.
As our customer, you can choose to provide us access to personal data of your own stakeholders (e.g. building users, employees). In these kinds of cases Caverion is a data processor and following your instructions for data handling.
Communication data (e.g. correspondence) (a)
Consent (a)
Contact details home (e.g. address, email, phone) (a)
Contact details work (e.g. address, email, phone) (a)
Demographic data (e.g. age, gender, nationality, language) (a)(b)
Diet (for events)(a)
Email tracking (e.g. open rates, clicks, date and time of your activities) (b)
Employer details (e.g. company name, address, previous employer) (a)(c)
Interests (a)(b)
IP address (b)
Name (e.g. first name, last name) (a)
Photos and videos (a)(c)
Position data (e.g. title, organizational unit, job)(a)(c)
Social media public profile data (b)
Survey response data (a)
System usage data (e.g. log-in times, action logs) (b)
User accounts (e.g. user name, password for system) (b) (c)
Web site visits (e.g. website, cookies, browser details, date and time of your visit, user behaviour) (b)
Purposes of collecting personal data
Advertising: We can use your personal information to display advertising on our website or on third party sites. Some of our third-party partners use cookies or similar technologies to provide you advertising based on your browsing activities and interests. Read more from our Cookie notice.
Communications & videoconferencing: We will store your contact information for communication purposes for contacting and co-operation.
Competitions: We may organise competitions where you submit your contact details when participating. We will use this information to be able to contact competition winner(s).
Complaints & claims: We need your personal data to help us manage your complaint, if you are not satisfied with us.
Customer service & support: We will use the information for customer relationship management and to be able to provide you customer service, support and execute our services to you. We can store information about your previous company to be able to identify our important customers and to maintain our customer relationship. We might inform you also about news or changes related to our products and services and be in contact with you on issues related to the customer relationship (e.g. remote management) or to deliver reports of our services.
Event management: We organise and host or participate to events and/or exhibitions. We use your information to e.g. invite you to events, share information about the events, ask for your feedback after the event and other event related purposes (e.g. special diets).
Feedback collection: We sometimes ask your feedback of various items. We use this information e.g. to improve our operations and performance.
Identity administration: We use this personal information to reliably identify you, in case of e.g. data subject requests, system access.
Improvement of our performance: We use personal data to improve our services, offering, customer experience and communication.
Internal training purposes: We might use your information for internal training purposes as an example to make ensure our employees have the knowledge and expertise they need to provide you the best possible performance.
Legal obligation: We will use your personal data to comply with the laws and regulations (e.g. court order).
Marketing: We might use your personal data for marketing purposes if you have indicated your consent and if we think our products, services, offers or third party solutions may interest you. We may also target specific marketing messages based on your user behaviour on our website. We might contact you about them through email, SMS or phone. You can Opt-out marketing communications at any time by filling out this form.
Read also our Cookie notice.
Offers & contract administration
Project management
Records & administration: We need to have comprehensive records of how we process your personal information.
Reporting and analytics: We sometimes use your information to reporting and analytics to enable us to improve our products, services and customer experience.
Risk assessments (e.g. financial risks)
Surveys: We may invite you to take part of our surveys. If you decide to take part we will use this information to improve our operations and performance.
4.3. Candidates
Information collected of you
When you apply for a job from Caverion, we need specific personal information from you. Based on your application and your given data, we will collect and use your personal data to check your suitability for possible jobs within the recruitment process. Some of the data, especially sensitive data, is collected only if you voluntarily provide this information in your application. We also create a candidate profile and candidate ID when you apply a job from Caverion.
Background checks (e.g. credit and criminal check, results of alcohol and drug testing) (c)
Communication data (e.g. recorded voice, correspondence) (a)
Competence data (e.g. education, competence & skills, permits, certifications, learning records) (a)(c)
Consent (a)
Contact details home (e.g. address, email, phone) (a)
Contact details work (e.g. address, email, phone) (a)
Demographic data (e.g. age, birth date, gender, nationality, language, marital status) (a)(b)
Family data (e.g. children) (a)
Identification (e.g. social security number or other identifier) (a)
IP address (b)
Name (e.g. first name, last name, other names) (a)
Photos and videos (a)
Position data (e.g. title, organisational unit, job) (a)
Previous employer details (e.g. company name, address) (a)
Recruitment data (e.g. CV, job application, selection information, job offer) (a)
Survey response data (a)
User accounts (e.g. user name, password for system) (b)(c)
Website visits (e.g. website cookies, browser details, date and time of your visits) (b)
We do not collect sensitive personal data unless you have voluntarily submitted it as part of application, given consent or alternative legitimate basis for processing exists.
Purposes of collecting personal data
Background checks
Communications & videoconferencing: We will store your contact information for communication purposes for contacting and co-operation.
Complaints & claims: We need your personal data to help us manage your complaint, if you are not satisfied with us.
Ensure compliance with company policies and legal requirements
Event management: We organise and host or participate to events and/or exhibitions. We use your information to e.g. invite you to events, share information about the events, and ask for your feedback after the event and other event related purposes (e.g. special diets).
Feedback collection: We sometimes ask your feedback of various items. We use this information e.g. to improve our operations and performance.
Identity administration: We use this personal information to reliably identify you, in case of e.g. data subject requests, system access.
Improve performance of the individual & the company
Internal training purposes: We might use your information for internal training purposes as an example to make ensure our employees have the knowledge and expertise they need to provide you the best possible performance.
Legal obligation: We will use your personal data to comply with the laws and regulations (e.g. court order).
Records and administration: We need to have comprehensive records of how we process your personal information.
Recruitment: We use this information in the job selection process and to be able to contact you and store your application.
Reporting and analytics: We sometimes use your information to reporting and analytics to enable us to improve our internal services.
Surveys: We may invite you to take part of our surveys. If you decide to take part we will use this information to improve our operations and performance.
Tests for evaluating  candidates (e.g. personality testing, ability and behaviour testing)
4.4. External workforce
Information collected of you
We are using your personal data while you are working for Caverion as an external workforce. We will only collect such personal information that is relevant for the purposes described in this privacy notice. Caverion will, when permitted or required by law, collect and maintain external workforce’s personal data for example in these cases:
Assignment data (e.g. assignment start date, end date, assignment type, contract-related agreements) (a) (c)
Background checks (e.g. credit and criminal  checks, results of alcohol and drug testing if done by Caverion) (c)
Communication data (e.g. recorded voice, correspondence, internal social media input) (a)
Competence data (e.g. education, competence & skills, permits, certifications, learning records) (a)(c)
Consent (a)
Contact details work (e.g. address, email, phone) (a) (c)
Demographic data (e.g. age, birth date, gender, nationality, language, marital status) (a) (b) (c)
Diet (for events) (a)
Email tracking data (e.g. open rates, clicks, date and time of your activities) (b)
Expenses data (e.g. travel or other expenses) (a) (c)
Facility access and usage (e.g. identification codes, passwords, information captured from security systems, including key card entry systems and CCTV, working time) (b) (c)
Identification (e.g. social security number or other identifier) (a)
IP address (b)
Name (e.g. first name, last name, other names) (a) (c)
Passport details (a)
Photos and videos (a) (c)
Physical measures (e.g. height, size) (a) (c)
Position data (e.g. title, organizational unit, cost centre, job, supervisor) (a) (c)
Recruitment data (e.g. CV, job application, selection information, job offer) (a) (c)
Safety data (e.g. accidents of the person) (a) (c)
Survey response data (a)
System usage data (e.g. log-in times, action logs) (b) (c)
User accounts (e.g. user name, password for system) (b) (c)
Vehicle data (e.g. license plate number, driving log) (a) (c)
Web site visits (e.g. website, cookies, browser details, date and time of your visit) (b)
Work permit (a) (c)
Work time reports and details (e.g. attendance, absence) (a) (b) (c)
We do not collect sensitive personal data unless you have voluntarily submitted it as part of application, given consent or alternative legitimate basis for processing exists.
Purposes of collecting personal data
Access management (e.g. company systems and facilities)
Background checks
Communications & videoconferencing: We will store your contact information for communication purposes for contacting and co-operation.
Competitions: We may organise competitions where you submit your contact details when participating. We will use this information to be able to contact competition winner(s).
Complaints & claims: We need your personal data to help us manage your complaint, if you are not satisfied with us.
Corporate travelling (e.g. travel planning, hotels, flights, car rentals, assisting in obtaining work-related travel documents, work permits)
Development & training
Emergency communication: We maintain emergency contact information to next of kin in case of emergency event.
Ensure compliance with company policies and legal requirements
Event management: We organise and host or participate to events and/or exhibitions. We use your information to e.g. invite you to events, share information about the events, and ask for your feedback after the event and other event related purposes (e.g. special diets).
Expense management (e.g. administration, expense reports, corporate credit cards, budgeting)
Feedback collection: We sometimes ask your feedback of various items. We use this information e.g. to improve our operations and performance.
Financial accounting
Identity administration: We use this personal information to reliably identify you, in case of e.g. data subject requests, system access.
Improve performance of the individual & the company
Insurance management
Internal auditing & security (e.g. internal investigations, compliance, risk management, conflict of interest reporting, occupational health and safety programs, safety measures to protect our employees, guests, facilities and assets)
Internal training purposes: We might use your information for internal training purposes as an example to make ensure our employees have the knowledge and expertise they need to provide you the best possible performance.
Invoicing & payments (e.g. phone invoices)
IT Support: We use your personal data to better solve your IT related problems.
Legal obligation: We will use your personal data to comply with the laws and regulations (e.g. court order).
Managing external workforce relationship (e.g. establishment, maintenance and termination of employment, disciplinary actions, assessment of qualifications for applicant, work related claims)
Procurement (e.g. working materials, services, equipment)
Project management
Providing work-ware: We use your personal data to assign you e.g. computer workstations, mobile phones, tablets, business cards.
Records & administration: We need to have comprehensive records of how we process your personal information.
Recruitment: We use this information in the job selection process and to be able to contact you and store your application.
Reporting and analytics: We sometimes use your information to reporting and analytics to enable us to improve our internal services.
Risk assessments
Safety reporting (e.g. work-related injuries)
Security of our working  facilities by controlling the access management
Surveys: We may invite you to take part of our surveys. If you decide to take part we will use this information to improve our operations and performance.
Test for evaluating external workforce (e.g. personality testing, ability and behaviour testing)
Website development: We use your information to improve our websites functionality, performance, user experience and security.
Workforce management (e.g. staffing, task monitoring, monitoring of working hours, work order management, workload management, headcount planning, termination, succession planning, absence monitoring, approval of workforce by our customer to their projects, video interviews in the recruiting process)
Work-ware usage tracking (e.g. equipment, hardware, software)
4.5. Vendors
Information collected of you
We are using your personal data while you are a vendor of Caverion. We will only collect such personal information that is relevant for the purposes described in this privacy notice. Caverion will, when permitted or required by law, collect and maintain vendor’s personal data for example in these cases:
Assignment data (e.g. assignment start date, end date, assignment type, contract-related agreements) (c)
Communication data (e.g. correspondence) (a)
Contact details work (e.g. address, email, phone) (a) (c)
Employer details (e.g. company name, address) (c)
Expenses data (c)
Name (e.g. first name, last name) (c)
Position data (e.g. title, organizational unit, job) (c)
Survey response data (a)
Purposes of collecting personal data
Communications & videoconferencing: We will store your contact information for communication purposes for contacting and co-operation.
Complaints & claims: We need your personal data to help us manage your complaint, if you are not satisfied with us.
Corporate travelling (e.g. travel planning, hotels, flights, car rentals, assisting in obtaining work-related travel documents, work permits if done by Caverion)
Ensure compliance with company policies and legal requirements
Event management: We organise and host or participate to events and/or exhibitions. We use your information to e.g. invite you to events, share information about the events,  and ask for your feedback after the event and other event related purposes (e.g. special diets).
Feedback collection: We sometimes ask your feedback of various items. We use this information e.g. to improve our operations and performance.
Identity administration: We use this personal information to reliably identify you, in case of e.g. data subject requests, system access.
Improve performance of the individual & the company
Internal training purposes: We might use your information for internal training purposes as an example to make ensure our employees have the knowledge and expertise they need to provide you the best possible performance.
Legal obligation: We will use your personal data to comply with the laws and regulations (e.g. court order).
Offers and contract administration
Project management
Records & administration: We need to have comprehensive records of how we process your personal information.
Reporting and analytics: We sometimes use your information to reporting and analytics to enable us to improve our internal services.
Risk assessments (e.g. financial risks)
Surveys: We may invite you to take part of our surveys. If you decide to take part we will use this information to improve our operations and performance.
4.6. Building visitors
Information collected of you
When you visit the facilities where Caverion operates, we ask you to provide us certain personal information.
Contact details work (e.g. address, email, phone) (a)
Employer details (e.g. company name, address) (a)
Facility access and usage (e.g. identification codes, passwords, information captured from security systems, including key card entry systems and CCTV, working time) (b) (c)
Name (e.g. first name, last name) (a)
Photos and videos (a) (c)
Position data (e.g. title, organizational unit, job) (a)
Survey response data (a)
Purposes of collecting personal data
Communications & videoconferencing: We will store your contact information for communication purposes for contacting and co-operation.
Complaints & claims: We need your personal data to help us manage your complaint, if you are not satisfied with us.
Feedback collection: We sometimes ask your feedback of various items. We use this information e.g. to improve our operations and performance.
Identity administration: We use this personal information to reliably identify you, in case of e.g. data subject requests, system access.
Improve performance of the individual & the company
Legal obligation: We will use your personal data to comply with the laws and regulations (e.g. court order).
Records & administration: We need to have comprehensive records of how we process your personal information.
Security of our working facilities by controlling the access management
Surveys: We may invite you to take part of our surveys. If you decide to take part we will use this information to improve our operations and performance.
5. Lawful basis for the processing
The applicable lawful basis for the processing of personal data depends on the circumstances relating to the relevant processing activities, as further described below:
5.1. Consent
If the processing of personal data is necessary for one or more specific purposes for which your consent is required, we will state so and obtain your consent, GDPR art. 6(1)(a) serves as the lawful basis for processing operations. We will ask your consent e.g. if we are going to use your photos or videos for marketing purposes or background checks.
5.2. Performance of a contract
If the processing of personal data is necessary for the performance of a contract, such as for providing certain services, to which the data subject is party, GDPR art. 6(1)(b) serves as the lawful basis for processing operations. The same applies to such processing operations which are necessary for carrying out pre-contractual measures, for example in the case of inquiries concerning our products or services.
5.3. Legal obligation
If the processing of personal data is necessary for complying with a legal obligation, such as for the fulfilment of tax obligations, GDPR art. 6(1)(c) serves as the lawful basis for processing operations.
5.4. Vital interests
If the processing of personal data is necessary for protecting the vital interests of a data subject, such as if a visitor were injured in our premises and his/her information would have to be passed on to medical personnel, GDPR art. 6(1)(d) serves as the lawful basis for processing operations.
5.5. Legitimate interests
If the processing of personal data is necessary for processing operations which are not covered by any of the abovementioned lawful basis, but are deemed permissible for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us, such as marketing activities if it has a minimal privacy impact, GDPR art. 6(1)(f) serves as the lawful basis for processing operations.
6. Disclosure and transfer of personal data
Caverion discloses and transfers information about personal data only with persons and companies who need to handle it. We ensure that the parties we disclose and transfer the information with are properly informed of our use of personal data and commit to comply with the restriction on use of that personal data, including keeping it confidential. Some stakeholders operate outside EU/EEA area, and we always disclose and transfer personal data to countries outside EU/EEA area in accordance with mandatory legislation and this privacy notice. For instance, if they are located in the United States, we can rely on the EU-US Privacy Shield if applicable.  We are disclosing and transferring, when needed, the personal data with these stakeholders:
6.1. Companies of Caverion Group
Due to our common IT infrastructure and knowledge sharing within the group, your personal data will be accessible by companies of Caverion Group for the listed purposes. Note that your personal data will be shared also outside the EU/EEA area, with our affiliates (e.g. Russia).
6.2. Suppliers and subcontractors
We are using external service providers for certain parts of business operations, e.g. IT system maintenance.
6.3. Third parties
We will share the data other partners or stakeholders. We also use cookies and web beacons on our websites and therefore share information with third parties collecting the data. Read our Cookie notice.
Below are the purposes of transferring personal data
Your request or consent: Based on your request or consent we can transfer your personal data.
Services provided to the company or our employees: We have suppliers that support our business operations, providing services on our behalf.
Acquisition, demerger or sale of business operations or companies: In case of acquisition, demerger or sale of the companies or other business operations, personal information is one of the transferred assets.
Information sharing from our collaboration partners: In some rare cases we may transfer your personal data for our collaboration partners to enable them to share information about their services.
Legal proceedings: When required by law or requirement by court, administrative agency or similar, we sometimes need to transfer your personal data to these parties. We can also share your personal data to seek for advice from lawyers or other professional advisers (banks, lawyers, accountants, potential buyers and vendors).
Protection of safety, facilities, privacy or rights of our stakeholders
Carry out other uses of personal data listed in the section “Purposes of collecting the data”
7. Your rights
You, as a data subject, have certain rights concerning your personal data.
7.1. Right to access, correct and object
You can contact us and we will inform what personal data we have collected and processed regarding you and the purposes such data are used for. You have the right to ask to correct any incorrect, incomplete, outdated or unnecessary personal data stored about you by contacting us. You can object to use of certain personal data, including direct marketing, if such data is processed for other purposes than purposes necessary for the performance of our services or for compliance with a legal obligation. You can also object any further processing of personal data after prior given consent. If you object to the further processing of personal data, this may lead to fewer possibilities to use our services.
7.2. Right to deletion and restriction of processing
You can also ask us to delete your personal data from our systems. We will comply with such request unless we have a legitimate ground not to delete the data. After the data has been deleted, we may not be able to delete immediately all residual copies from our active servers and backup systems. Such copies shall be deleted as soon as reasonably possible. Even though you can request us to restrict processing of certain personal data; this may however lead to fewer possibilities to use our website and other services.
7.3. Right to data portability
You have the right to receive personal data provided by you to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format when the data is processed automatically and is processed based on consent or fulfilment of contract or steps preparatory to a contract.
These rights (7.1.-7.3.) can be exercised by using the Data Subject Request form. We can request the provision of additional information necessary to confirm your identity. We can also reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, excessive or manifestly unfounded. After receiving all the required information of your request (incl. validation of identity), we’ll start the processing of your request. We’ll do our best effort to process your request within a period of one (1) month. If we for some reason cannot process your request within the planned schedule, we will inform you about the delay as soon as possible within that one (1) month period. The maximum delivery time of the request will be three (3) months.  It’s worth noting that if you request access, rectification, restriction or deletion of personal data, we might in some cases not be required to do so according to applicable law.
7.4. Consents
If the personal data you have given us is based on your consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. You can opt-out your digital marketing consent here.
If you have given consent for visual materials (images, videos) or contents (blog posts, articles), you can withdraw your consent here. Note that processing your personal data is necessary for us to provide you our products and services. Withdrawing your consent may lead to a situation where we cannot necessarily provide you our services.
7.5. Complaints
If you are not satisfied with the decision or actions of Caverion, you have always right to lodge a complaint to local data protection authority.
8. Cookies and Beacons
We use cookies and beacons on our websites. Please see our Cookie notice.
9. Retention of personal data
We have the right to store your personal data as long as needed for legitimate purpose or as long as required by law. The criteria used to determine the period of storage of personal data is the respective statutory retention period and legitimate purpose. We sometimes need to keep your personal data after the end of the employment relationship to comply with our legal obligations and/or to resolve possible disputes. The information and the length of the storage time vary depending on the data in question and applicable law. Detailed retention times can be provided upon request. We continuously erase and/or anonymise your personal data when it is no longer relevant for the purposes for which we are processing it.
10. Changes to privacy notice
We reserve the right to review, modify and update this privacy notice from time to time. If we make such changes, we will record the date of the amendment or modification to this privacy notice. Please review this privacy notice regularly and especially before submitting any personal data to us. In case of updates to this privacy notice, we will not alert our users for all the updates but if there are really important changes to the privacy notice or how we use your information, we will utilise commercially reasonable efforts to provide appropriate notification to you.
Would you like to hear more about our service areas or disciplines?
